[{"answer": "Well, the 1 percent, they have about 40 percent of all the wealth in this country.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Who are the 1 percent?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Well, it depends on who you asked.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Is this really a protest against capitalism, as some have been saying, or is it a protest against capitalist greed and abuse of capitalism?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "What's wrong with me?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "I'm not in the 1 percent.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "You're in the 1 percent, right?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Probably 0.2 percent?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Of course I'm not.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "You're not in if 1 percent?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Because you're worth millions.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "How can I be in the 1 percent?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "No, I'm asking if you accept that.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Well, then if you believe that about me, then that's really something, isn't it?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Hi.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Where is Monica?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Well, for me, I mean, I am a person with a master's degree who has been unemployed since I graduated.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What do you think the answer is?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "I think there is some of that.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Are there lots of people to blame?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "If you were slicing a pie up, how would you fairly do it?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "But just a sense of where you think the majority of blame lies here?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Well, they have.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "As far as blaming the American people, I mean, haven't they been through enough really?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Nobody went against probably all the guidelines from their parents?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "I mean there has to be some sense of self-blame, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, it's one of the answers, yes.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "And what is the simple answer to getting America back to work?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Well, I think that it's very hard to find a job, no matter what you've got, whether you have a high school education or a master's.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "What is your view of the jobs crisis and where the president now is on this?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I think computers have changed the world.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "What's your gut feeling?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, that's a good thing.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "What do you do about the fact that computers can now do, in some cases, the jobs of a thousand people?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Why are they holding on to the money?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "My biggest concern, obviously, I'm not going to be able to find a job.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What's been your concern?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I'll be close to probably 50, 60,000.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "How much debt have you wracked up?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "And where they have to go out into the real world at 22 years old or 24 with this crushing debt.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "And you know how can America compete if the brains of the country are being treated in this way?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well, I see increasingly a lot.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Now you've come from a country where -- you know, how much debt do students have when they're 23 years old and they leave university?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "A thousand dollars.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Or a city school here, huh?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "If I were president -- and I'm not announcing, by the way, on your show.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Well, you haven't been poor.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "I mean would she be better off being poorer?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "They would get -- they would get no help and they would have Republican candidates saying, well, that's your own problem.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "They wouldn't get the funding, wouldn't they?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "It's very important.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "How important is the tax issue?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Because the wealthy have not been paying their fair share.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Well, no, I mean --", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "What was wrong with the way we used to have it?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Let's not be too --", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Really, what was wrong?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Let's not be too rose tipped it, because there would be people from previous generations who will have a myriad of problems, too.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "With that?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Well, the thing, again, when we were growing up, there was a system that said -- I mean the way I described it, I think I might have said this last time I was on the show, that the contract with the workers, between the workers and the owners was that if you the worker have worked hard and the company prospered, you prospered.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "What is a good capitalist?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I blame myself part of it, absolutely.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Who do you blame?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Do you have any confidence that people are going to come up with answers to get you out of this problem?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't know.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "What do you think has happened to the American dream?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, my loan was, you know, underperforming.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Hello.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Mr. Perkins?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I think that their message should be more defined.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Is the message clear?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Well, I think a lot of it is.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "How big a part of this is disquiet and concern over health care in this country, do you think?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "I mean this is -- this is -- we're not going to take this anymore, we're not going to listen to this kind of argument because these are the victims of this and they are -- and fortunately -- can I just say one thing -- good news?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "Mr. Mooney?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "You know, you know how all Americans feel or just how you feel in California?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "I live in Michigan, thank you, though.", "docId": "111025pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Very quickly, Michael, your response?", "qSentId": 731}]